He's about to fall in love with the most scandalous woman of his time.
Impromptu is a drama, comedy, music film directed by James Lapine.
In 1830s France, pianist/composer Frédéric Chopin is pursued romantically by the
determined, individualistic woman who uses the name George Sand.
George Sand, played by Judy Davis.
Frederic Chopin, played by Hugh Grant.
Alfred De Musset, played by Mandy Patinkin.
Marie D'Agoult, played by Bernadette Peters.
Franz Liszt, played by Julian Sands.
Eugene Delacroix, played by Ralph Brown.
Impromptu is a 1991 period drama film directed by James Lapine,
written by Sarah Kernochan, produced by Daniel A.
Sherkow and Stuart Oken, and starring Hugh Grant as
Frédéric Chopin and Judy Davis as George Sand.
It was shot entirely on location in France as a
British production by an American company.
Its main filming location was at the Château des
Briottières outside Angers, in the Loire Valley.
The film explores themes of countryside, duel, novelist, cross dresser, duchess.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.